Krishna only wants love and affection.
Krishna vuole solo amore ed affetto.
[Heart to Heart Connection]
[Connessione Da Cuore a Cuore]
Whether it is from Chinese, American, Russian, Indian.
Che sia dai cinesi, dagli americani, dai russi, dagli indiani.
This theme about heart ...
Questa questione del cuore...
Krishna consciousness is a heart to heart connection.
La coscienza di Krishna è una connessione da cuore a cuore.
So only the body is a Chinese body, a Thai body, American body,
Dunque solo il corpo è un corpo cinese, un corpo thailandese, un corpo americano,
but there is not a Chinese soul, American soul, Thai soul, Indian soul ...
ma non c'è un'anima cinese, un'anima americana, un'anima thailandese, un'anima indiana...
Like we say, “For every action equal opposite reaction.”
Si dice: «Per ogni azione c'è una reazione uguale e contraria».
So there is some action in the past
Allora ci sono state azioni in passato
that necessitated that someone is born in China,
che hanno richiesto che qualcuno nascesse in Cina,
someone’s born in Thailand, someone’s born in America,
qualcuno nascesse in Thailandia, qualcuo nascesse in America,
someone’s born in Russia.
qualcuno nascesse in Russia.
But the important thing to understand is the heart to heart connection.
Ma la cosa importante da capire è la connessione da cuore a cuore.
From the heart of Krishna to the heart of the devotee.
Dal cuore di Krishna al cuore del devoto.
And that transcends geography, politics,
E questa trascende la geografia, la politica,
geopolitical, socio-economic circumstances.
la geopolitica, le circostanze socio-economiche.